To a degree, this is the future of content and opinions and late night and all of that s**t.
Social media has made it so anybody with a microphone and a good opinion matters.
So if you do that, you don't necessarily need a desk and a studio audience and a glossy, glittery floor.
It's true.
Well, even in producing in Amanda We Trust, right?
The reality of it being done was literally just because there was no one to have notes with.
So you're telling me when you reached out to Rashida that you didn't have three hours of pre-call interviews?
No.
And honestly, I think there wasn't because they were like, oh, this isn't a big old network that we're dealing with.
The type of red tape and things that we would need to clear, like we don't need to.
We trust Amanda's voice.
And so we're going to stick with that.
And I think that not being aligned with a network to a degree is going to give certain creators more access.
People say content is king.
Okay, but audience is power.
If you have an audience and you have a point of view, then people are going to rock with you.